(This story is entirely fictional)
(Based on the novel
Doctor Qin: Executer)
(Welcome to my gallery,)
(Mr. Zhang, the great collector.)
(What's playing now)
(is your favorite piece.)
Who are you?
(Now,)
(you have to play a game with me.)
Who on earth are you?
What do you want?
(First, pick up the object beside you.)
(The rules are simple.)
(Beside you is your beloved Starlight.)
(But its battery only lasts
ten minutes.)
(In the sunflowers across from you,)
(six petals hold)
(secrets she wants to tell you.)
(Find them)
(and put them in the right order)
(in the empty display frames
behind you.)
(Bring back one petal at a time.)
(You have sixty minutes.)
(If you fail,)
(all your collections)
(will be put on public display.)
(The countdown)
(begins now.)
(60:00)
(59:59)
(59:58)
(59:57)
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 11=
The facial reconstruction
from the skull is in.
The victim is... Zhang Xiaoya?
How could it be Zhang Xiaoya?
(50:36)
(50:35)
(50:34)
(50:33)
(How does it feel?)
(Does it feel good?)
(1)
(7)
(5)
(30:36)
(30:35)
(30:34)
(You don't have much time left.)
(Hurry up.)
(02:10; Error)
(00:33; Error)
Why is it wrong?
(Only ten seconds left.)
(Ten.)
(Nine.)
(Eight.)
(Seven.)
(Six.)
(Five.)
(Four.)
(Three.)
(Two.)
(Correct)
(One.)
(So you haven't forgotten it.)
(July 15, 2015)
(was your daughter
Zhang Xiaoya's birthday)
(and the day she died.)
(Dad,)
(you're a great hero,)
(a great charity donor,)
(and the person I admired most!)
You're nothing but a hypocrite.
You're the devil.
You're a demon!
(Serve with Loyalty and Innovation)
She got here at dawn.
She's been keeping us up all night.
She refuses to go home,
saying a female ghost is after her.
By the way, she said she's Xu Meng.
Xu Meng?
We've been looking for her for ages.
Any history of drug use?
We tested her.
Negative.
Her eye whites are bloodshot,
and her dark circles are severe.
She's been suffering
from long-term sleep problems.
Her frown lines are pronounced,
and her lips are very dry.
She's clearly anxious.
Based on all these signs,
she's likely been suffering
from a sleep disorder
for three to six months.
Let's go in and ask her.
Come on, Ziyan.
We're with
the Longfan Criminal Investigation Team.
I'm Han Liang.
What are you afraid of?
Tell us. Maybe we can help.
A... a voice.
It sounds like a girl crying.
No, humming a song.
Xu Meng,
tell us.
What kind of girl was she?
Do you recognize the voice?
It's... it's Zhang Xiaoya.
It has to be her.
Yes. That's exactly who I saw!
She's come back for me.
Zhang Xiaoya?
What did you do to her?
Our records show
you were an early beneficiary
of Zhang Xiaodong's charity fund.
So, what do you remember
about Mr. Zhang or his family?
Say, his daughter,
Zhang Xiaoya?
Nothing.
Just a regular sponsorship.
I barely ever saw them.
If you weren't close,
why would you be afraid?
Unless your time with her
or what happened to her
was far more serious.
Have you been to Fengshan Villa
for Zhang Xiaoya's birthday before?
Xu Meng.
Tell me.
What exactly happened at Fengshan Villa
ten years ago?
What happened that night,
on her birthday?
Meng.
Where's Xiaoxue?
Why wasn't she there for the cake?
Is she still feeling sick?
I should go check on her.
What's wrong, Meng?
Why are you crying?
Let's go find her together, okay?
What's wrong?
Xiaoya,
are we besties?
Of course we are.
You, me, and Xiaoxue.
The three of us.
Didn't we promise
to be besties for life?
Meng.
Don't cry.
What's wrong?
Tell me what happened.
Okay?
Where did Zhang Xiaoya go?
Did she go to question her father?
That night at Fengshan Villa,
you were the last one,
or one of the few,
to know Zhang Xiaoya went to her father.
And then something happened to her,
right?
How did you become friends
with Zhang Xiaoya?
(Debt Offset Service Agreement)
Sign the contracts.
I'll keep my promise to you.
But keep this confidential.
Ms. Su!
Xiaoya?
Why are you back?
Weren't you taking IELTS classes?
It was so boring,
so I snuck back.
Ms. Su,
please don't tell my dad.
Please.
You're the best!
All right.
Who are they?
Them?
They're students your father sponsors.
Hi.
I'm Zhang Xiaoya.
Hi. I'm Xiaoxue.
Just call me Meng.
What are you doing?
I hate that my dad drinks.
When he gets drunk,
he has even less time for me.
He's barely home.
When he is, he just stays in his room.
Let me pour them all out.
Oh my God!
This bottle costs thousands of euros!
Who cares?
Come on. Help me pour them all.
You know what?
My dad secretly keeps
a bunch of crocodiles in the pool.
Let's see if they get drunk
and come charging at us.
It's pretty good.
Let me try it.
Have some.
It tastes good!
Drink up.
Do crocodiles really eat people?
I don't know if crocodiles eat people,
but I'll eat you first.
Three, two, one!
Xiaoya was a kind and innocent girl.
After discovering
something so horrifying,
would she just let it go?
What could she have said to her father?
An argument?
A confrontation?
Where were you
at the time?
Were you right there with her?
I...
I just wanted to follow her.
I was afraid she'd...
Afraid of what?
That something might happen to her?
So what did you see?
It... it was Zhang Xiaodong.
What's wrong?
Who upset my little princess?
Tell me.
What did you do to Xiaoxue?
Xiaoya,
some things are complicated.
It's not what you think.
I'm disgusted.
This family, and you,
all disgust me!
Enough!
You shouldn't ask about this.
Go back to your room.
I always thought
you were the person I admired most.
you were a great charity donor!
Did you...
- Did you...
- Shut up!
What do you know?
To build this whole business,
I need to entertain people
and grease some palms.
They get financial support,
so they owe me something in return.
That's only fair.
Without me, they're nothing!
- Nothing!
- I'm calling the police.
I'll tell everyone
- what kind of person you are!
- You dare!
Get back here!
Let go of me!
Xiaoya, have you lost your mind?
- You're a wolf in sheep's clothing.
- Zhang Xiaoya...
You're a hypocrite!
Xiaoya!
Please, honey.
Don't call the police.
If you do, we're all finished.
Please?
I did all this
for you,
for this family.
For me?
Or for yourself?
- You know the answer!
- It was all for you!
It had nothing to do with me!
- Can't you stop being so stubborn?
- You did it for yourself!
Can't you listen to me for once?
Can't you try to understand me?
Zhang Xiaoya had an accident.
What about Xiaoxue?
Did she know about that?
Where did she go?
I...
I never saw her again.
Xu Meng,
think carefully before you answer me.
I really haven't seen her again.
Then do you know He Guifen is dead?
I know!
She deserved it.
She's the one
who pushed me into hell!
It was all for money.
She deserved to be scammed!
She was murdered.
Xu Meng,
someone's avenging your past.
Do you know that?
(I will gather evidence)
(and make them pay.)
(Later I fled Longfan)
(and never contacted her again.)
(But one day...)
What was the evidence
she talked about?
I don't know.
Xiaoxue had a USB drive.
She always kept it on her.
What was on the USB drive?
I didn't dare ask.
I didn't even dare think about it.
I just wanted to pretend
that time never happened.
Xiaoxue?
Xiaoxue...
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
♪I turned around,
and a gunshot rang out♪
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪Years later, when we meet again♪
♪Don't mention this moonlit night♪
♪The waves smooth
two lines of footprints♪
♪Half a cup of sweetness
sinks into the sand♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪Wind back to shore,
clouds back to hills♪
♪We stop here in this night♪
♪This is the past, the only,
the last look back♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪